I think that education has to be changed.
And, in fact, there is something that can—and even must—revolutionize education.
The very shape that a new education will take, I have no idea.
But I think there is a revolution already on its way,
and it's dominating now, through the nature and diffusion of information
now possible thanks to the Internet.
Then, what we have right now, is a very powerful tool, the Internet,
and it makes possible for us, as teachers, who are not professionals of technology,
to have easy access to a tool for making projects,
and that result is that it will be more easy to visualize and share.
The word "sharing" on the Internet is incredible.
Universities today are unable to keep up with the rapid developments or
adjust their curricula fast enough.
It will be very important in the future that we dont strictly depend on such universities
but rather we need to create informal educational environments, establish peer-to-peer learning,
and also accept alternative academic certifications.
Schools were teaching things that were obsolete ten years ago.
Because far as I'm concerned, the future is people teaching other people
using open web tools for helping each other,
and teaching each other open technologies,
and therefore inventing new things and new jobs.
I think the only way learning works is through a joyful insurgency.
By that I mean, it's not just rebelling against systems that exist,
but modeling the kind of excitement that comes from the spirit of trying something new
and really looking for a different kind of learning altogether.